# **Summary**

Tech project manager seeks new role in management or communications. Open to a wide range of positions, including (but not limited to) product, project, and executive management, as well as business/data analysis. Previous experience in project management, tech development, and seed-stage ventures.

## Work Experience

### **Tech Consultant** – Capgemini US, New York NY

Jun. 2022 – Present

# **Data Analyst**

- Cleaned and structured data for use in one of Capgemini's internal data analysis tools.
- Presented analysis findings to client.

### **Scrum Master (Project Manager)**

- Facilitated Scrum (project management) practices for client's machine learning team, including scheduling, goal setting, collaboration, and documentation.
- Developed Microsoft Azure DevOps Dashboards, Queries, Roadmaps, etc. to optimize team efficiency.
- Calculated and analyzed sprint metrics such as velocity and accuracy.

Certifications: PMS1 Scrum Master, AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

### Data Analyst Intern – NYU Leslie Entrepreneurial Institute, New York NY

Apr. 2021 - May 2022

# **Community Programs Intern**

#### Office Intern

- Analyzed aggregate data from Institute events by creating a behavioral network with Python's PyVis library.
- Developed software to clean, organize, and analyze data.
- Completed several interim assignments and a final project report presented to Institute staff.

### Education

### New York University, Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences

Sep. 2018 - May 2022

GPA: 3.6

Major in Computer Science

Minors in Mathematics and Italian

Academic Memberships: Tech@NYU, NYU Entrepreneurs Network, Bite Club at NYU

Societies: LGBTQ+ in Tech, Botmakers

Coding Languages: Python, Java, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, C/C++

# **Projects**

## Network Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Created a behavioral network from event data for NYU's Entrepreneurial Institute.
- Developed adjacency data and network visualization to demonstrate trends in the data.

# Movie Review Sentiment Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Calculated binary classification and logistic regression to determine sentiment for 50,000 IMDb movie reviews.
- Used machine learning tools such as SciKit Learn, Jupyter Notebook, and NLTK to parse reviews and perform analysis.

### **Daily Tarot Bot**

- Created a Twitter bot that tweets a tarot card once a day with meaningful advice.
- Learned Python's Tweepy library, GitHub Actions flows, project scheduling, API handling, and version control.